<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/><updated>2018-01-17T21:13:21-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Artemis Hub</title><subtitle>Welcome! This is my place on the web for projects, blogging, and anything else I can include. A short description about me, I'm a Third year Software Eng. student at UOIT in Oshawa. To hear more about myself, check out this blog post.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Stock View</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/01/10/stock-view/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Stock View"/><published>2018-01-10T16:15:05-05:00</published><updated>2018-01-10T16:15:05-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/01/10/stock-view</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/01/10/stock-view/">&lt;p&gt;Financial Stock tracking application made using Python Flask.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Financial Stock tracking application made using Python Flask.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/stockview.png"/></entry><entry><title type="html">All about me!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/01/10/about-me/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="All about me!"/><published>2018-01-10T16:15:05-05:00</published><updated>2018-01-10T16:15:05-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/01/10/about-me</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/01/10/about-me/">&lt;p&gt;So I see you’re interested in learning more about me! I am a third year Software Engineering student at UOIT (University of Ontario Institute of Technology). My interests include data science, data visualization, and artificial intelligence. Currently, I am searching for a summer coop as a developer.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4 id=&quot;professional-work&quot;&gt;Professional Work&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;I have worked at &lt;strong&gt;The Computer Geek&lt;/strong&gt; since May 2015. It is a Web Solutions company based in Ajax, ON. They offer a variety of different experiences, mostly working as a freelance organization. I was a Back End Developer with a focus on fixing e-commerce and forum sites, creating static html sites, and adding functionality to sites based on client demand. I have worked with various kinds of CMS’s, including WordPress, Jhoomla, and Drupal to name a few. This opportunity also increased my knowledge related to interacting with API’s from various companies, like Paypal and UPS. I also practiced my communication skills through client interactions via email or phone, and between team members to stay on the same page.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4 id=&quot;university-efforts&quot;&gt;University Efforts&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;I am currently the VP of Finance for the IEEE Student Branch at UOIT. I manage the budgets for any equipment and events that take place, as well as handle follow-up documentation. I am also in the running to be the Chair for the 2018-2019 school year. My secondary role is to manage the &lt;strong&gt;website&lt;/strong&gt;; this includes keeping it up to date with current events, activities, and opportunities that students at UOIT can look forward to. I have participated in the previous two &lt;strong&gt;IEEExtreme competitions&lt;/strong&gt;. Having an interest in the competition, it was also my duty to organize the event.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4 id=&quot;personal-adventures&quot;&gt;Personal Adventures&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;In Jan 2017, my team and I went to Pennsylvania for PennApps. We successfully created an image classification app for dog breeds which was wrapped in a mobile app as a community based lost dog finding app, &lt;strong&gt;Whereis.dog&lt;/strong&gt;. Later in the same month, I attended OEC 2017 at Carleton University. We were assigned to create an optimal solution for an energy grid system, allowing for energy to flow with the shortest delay even with shut downs at randomly selected locations. This task was to be completed overnight, and presented the next day. This also included creating a GUI, for which we used React and Vis.js.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4 id=&quot;skills-and-work-environment&quot;&gt;Skills and Work Environment&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;I have worked in a multitude of programming languages for work and course assignments. Being a web developer, I have worked a lot with the LAMP stack. Currently, my interests lie in learning Python for AI and Data Science, as well as JavaScript for building full stack Web apps. I have experience with Windows, Linux, and MacOS; my setup as of now is a 2017 Macbook Pro using High Sierra.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Recently, I took the Jose Padilla Data Science course on Udemy which teaches you how to use visualization and data manipulation libraries with Python. This included Pandas, Seaborn and Plotly to name a few.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4 id=&quot;interests-and-future-projects&quot;&gt;Interests and Future Projects&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;My goal is to create user friendly, data visualizations using public data. I have an interest in the financial markets, which lead me to think up the Stock View project. That was developed for a course alongside my classmates. Look forward to more interesting projects and implementations from me!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">So I see you’re interested in learning more about me! I am a third year Software Engineering student at UOIT (University of Ontario Institute of Technology). My interests include data science, data visualization, and artificial intelligence. Currently, I am searching for a summer coop as a developer.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/contact3.jpg"/></entry></feed>